I'm back.
내가 돌아왔다
Hey, everyone.
다들, 안녕?
Hey, how could you abandon me like that?
야, 어떻게 날 그렇게 내버릴 수 있지?
But I'm back now!
하지만 난 이제 돌아왔다!
Behold, the 7.6 billion people of the world!
보아라, 76억의 세계인아!
Nineteen years late, but the feared king returns!
19년이 늦었지만 두려운 왕이 귀환했다
You shall look at me for a glimpse of Angolmois!
'앙골모아'를 보고 싶으면 나를 보라고!
This is my latest ultimate killer technique!
이건 내 최신 필살기다!
Super, delicious, cosmic, golden,
최강 맛있고 우주적이고 황금빛이고
special reserve, gorgeous, ultra, hyper-mega,
특별히 남겨둔 아름다운 울트라 초대형으로
marvelous, fantastic,
경이롭고 환상적인
overload, Giga Drill meteor!
과부하 걸린 '기가 드릴 별똥별'이다!
No problem, c'est bon, está bien, everything's all right!
문제없어, 아주 좋아 다 잘된 거야!
Finally! The ultimate Jashin-chan dropkick!
드디어! 최후의 사신짱 드롭킥이다!
My Noel!
나의 노엘!
Hey, everyone!
안녕하세요, 여러분!
Thank you so much!
정말 고맙습니다!
This can't be!
이럴 수가!
Sorry, ma'am.
죄송해요, 할머니
We won't forget again.
다시는 잊지 않을게요
Don't worry about it.
아니야, 괜찮아
Congratulations!
축하합니다!
We have a jackpot here!
잭폿이 터졌습니다!
Here's your prize.
상품을 받으세요
A two-day VIP experience at a private beach!
개인 전용 해변에서 2일간 VIP 경험을 하세요
Damn it.
젠장
END
'끝'
Beth!
베이트
It's time to eat!
저녁 시간이다
Huh?
어?
Did you get bigger...?
너 큰 거야...?
I feel like she was smaller before I went to space.
내가 우주로 가기 전엔 더 작았던 거 같은데
That means we gotta build you a bigger house.
우리가 더 큰 집을 네게 만들어줘야겠지?
I keep forgetting she's the Beast of Gévaudan.
얘가 '제보당의 괴수'인 걸 자꾸 잊는단 말이야
Forget the house, we're gonna need a cage.
집이 아니라 우리에 가둬야 해
How the hell am I supposed to control such a big beast?
그렇게 큰 괴수를 내가 어떻게 다루겠어?
I'll end up as her dinner!
내가 쟤에게 저녁거리로 먹힐 거야!
I'll get rid of her while I can!
할 수 있을 때 처리해야지!
It's been a drag taking you on walks,
힘들게 널 산책시키고
feeding you expensive food... Now's the perfect time.
비싼 음식을 먹였지... 지금이 완벽한 때다
Goodbye, Beth!
잘 가라, 베이트!
Equally fatal as my infamous dropkick!
내 악명높은 드롭킥과 맞먹는
The Royal Copenhagen!
로열코펜하겐이다!
Don't look so innocent when I'm about to kill you!
내가 널 죽이기 직전인데 순진한 표정 짓지 마
She completely trusts me as her owner.
얘는 내가 주인이라고 완전히 믿는다
But I can't afford to wait any longer.
하지만 난 더 기다릴 수 없어
How could I do that to you?
내가 어떻게 너에게 그럴 수 있겠니?
I've gotten so attached while taking care of her.
이 애를 돌보는 동안 정이 너무 깊이 들었어
A lordly beast is living,
위풍당당한 괴수가
leashed up, stripped of freedom.
줄에 묶여 자유를 빼앗긴 채로 산다
You're just like me.
넌 나와 같은 신세구나
I'm sorry, Beth.
미안해, 베이트
What is it?
왜 그래?
Quit that! That tickles.
하지 마! 간지럽다니까
I said stop-- Huh?
하지 말랬지... 어?
She needs to die, now!
저 애는 지금 죽어야 해!
I still got my left hand.
아직 왼손이 남았다
Take this! The Lefty Royal Copenhagen!
받아라! 왼손 로열코펜하겐이다!
No effect at all.
전혀 소용없군
-Hello there. -Huh?
- 안녕 - 응?
Yurine!
유리네!
It's been a while.
오랜만이다
Weren't you lonely without me?
나 없어서 외롭지 않았니?
You were gone? I didn't even notice.
어디 갔었어? 난 알지도 못했는데?
What do you mean? I was gone for three light-years!
무슨 소리야? 내가 3광년이나 없었는데!
You have no idea what I went through to come back!
다시 돌아오려고 어떤 일을 겪었는지 네가 알아?
I really don't care. Oh, you dropped this.
난 정말 관심 없다 참, 너 이거 떨어뜨렸어
Right! Beth is getting bigger and stronger!
맞아! 베이트가 점점 커지고 힘도 강해져
She's becoming a huge threat
대단한 위협이 될 거야
to our lives...?
우리 목숨에...?
There, there. Good girl.
그래, 그래 아주 착하지
Don't ignore me.
날 무시하지 마
Now, since you punched Beth earlier...
자, 네가 베이트에게 주먹을 날렸으니까...
In the name of Beth, I will punish you!
베이트의 이름으로 내가 너를 벌주겠다
I'm the victim here!
피해자는 나야!
I don't deserve the punishment!
난 벌 받을 짓 안 했어!
I'll punish you!
널 처벌할 거다
I give up. She's completely lost her mind.
관두자 쟤는 완전히 정신이 나갔어
No use talking.
말해봐야 소용없지
Which do you prefer? A punch or a kick?
네가 골라 주먹으로 맞을래? 차일래?
What's your preference?
뭐가 더 좋지?
A punch.
주먹이군
Now, it's dinner time for us too.
이제 우리도 저녁 먹어야지
I'll fix you up with superglue so make sure to bring it.
초강력 접착제로 고쳐줄 테니까 그걸 꼭 가져와
Crazy bitch.
정신 나간 계집애
Coming up, the swimsuit edition!
다음은 '수영복 판'입니다!
Don't miss it!
놓치지 마세요!
There's nobody here but us!
여긴 우리 말고 아무도 없다!
Can't believe she won a free private beach trip for six
스즈란 쇼핑 구역 경품 행사에서 유리네가 전용 해변으로
in the Suzuran Shopping District raffle!
6명이 가는 무료 여행에 당첨된 걸 믿을 수가 없어
Yurine has great luck!
유리네에겐 엄청난 행운이 따라!
Of course I do.
물론이지
Smile!
스마일!
Yay!
야호!
Lord, please forgive me.
신이시여, 제발 저를 용서하소서
I've surrendered to the devil's temptation yet again.
제가 악마의 유혹에 또 굴복했습니다
I, Pekola, am a sinful angel.
저, 페코라는 죄지은 천사입니다
But who could say no to barbeque?
하지만 바비큐 초대를 누가 거절할 수 있나요?
Look at this beach.
이 해변을 봐
It's been 3000 years since I went swimming in the Dead Sea.
내가 마지막으로 수영하러 사해에 갔던 게 3,000년 전이지
The Dead Sea is a lake, not an ocean.
사해는 바다가 아니라 호수입니다
-Keep the beach clean, guys. -Got it!
- 해변은 더럽히지 마, 얘들아 - 알겠어!
Oh, yeah.
그래
-Bring back all the trash. -Got it!
- 쓰레기는 다 가져가야 해 - 그래!
I noticed there's a new devil in the mix.
저들 중에 새 악마가 눈에 띈다
-Jashin-chan! -What?
- 사신짱! - 왜?
Your swimsuit is adorable!
네 수용복이 정말 예쁘다
It's not adorable, it's strong!
예쁜 게 아니라 튼튼한 거야
Did you really need to wear that?
넌 꼭 그걸 입어야겠니?
Who doesn't wear a swimsuit to the beach?
해변에서 수영복을 안 입는 사람이 어디 있어?
We never see eye to eye.
우리는 정말 안 통한다
Pekola!
페코라!
Yes?
응?
Well, that was suspicious.
뭐야, 의심스럽군
-Jashin-chan. -It's nothing.
- 사신짱 - 아무것도 아니야
-What's up? -What is it?
- 왜 그래? - 그게 뭐지?
What are you hiding? Show us!
뭘 숨기는 거야? 보여줘!
No! Please stop.
안 돼! 제발 하지 마
No need to be shy. What have you got to lose?
부끄러워하지 마 잃을 것도 없잖아?
Stop!
그러지 마!
Don't be obnoxious.
무례하게 굴지 마
Tajiri?
다지리?
Your last name is Tajiri?
네 성이 '다지리'야?
Pekola Tajiri, huh?
다지리 페코라?
Hello there.
처음 뵙습니다
I'm Persephone II, the devil who came from hell
전 페르세포네 2세죠 지옥에서 사신짱을 찾아온
to look for Jashin-chan.
악마입니다
Nice to meet you, Ms. Tajiri!
만나서 반갑습니다, 다지리 씨
Nice to meet-- No!
반가워... 아니야!
I just borrowed this from a co-worker.
이건 동료에게서 빌린 수영복이야
You know I don't have a last name.
알잖아, 난 성이 없어
Really, Tajiri?
정말이야, 다지리?
-Got it, Tajiri. -Tajiri-chan.
- 알았다, 다지리짱 - 다지리짱
Stop calling me Tajiri!
다지리라고 부르지 마!
Hey, Pekola.
있지, 페코라
I just... I just wanted to say you look cute in a swimsuit too.
난 그저... 수영복 입은 네가 예쁘다고 말하려던 거야
Really?
정말?
It's true.
그건 사실이다
You should be punished for it.
넌 벌을 받아야 해
It looks too good on you, Pekola.
네게 너무 잘 어울려, 페코라
I'm so cute!
난 정말 예뻐!
I can't wear sandals so the sand feels hot!
난 샌들을 못 신는데 모래가 뜨거워
Catch me if you can!
나 잡아봐라!
Jashin-chan! You have to warm up first!
사신짱, 준비 운동부터 해
Not listening!
안 들린다
Vega pose!
베가 자세!
One, two, three, four!
하나, 둘, 셋, 넷!
Warm-ups are crucial.
준비운동은 꼭 해야 해
-Yup! -Yes.
- 응! - 그래
My foot, I mean, my tail's cramped up!
내 발에, 그게 아니라 내 꼬리에 쥐가 난다
Looks so fun, I'm so jealous.
재밌겠다, 너무 부러워
But since I can't swim, I'll make a sand castle.
난 수영을 못 하니까 모래성을 만들어야지
Scoop, scoop, scoop!
모래를 판다 파고 또 판다
That was a close call.
아슬아슬했다
Ice! Ice!
얼음요! 얼음
How about some refreshing shaved ice?
상큼한 빙수를 드세요
Hey, it's Yusa and Koji.
어이, 유사와 코지
-Welcome. -Yes, yes!
- 어서 오세요 - 그래, 그래!
Yes, yes! How about an exciting French kiss?
그래, 그거다! 신나는 프렌치 키스는 어때?
Or do you prefer an unforgettable deep kiss?
아니면 기억에 남는 진한 키스가 더 좋니?
Actually, they're the same thing.
실제로 그 둘은 같은 것이죠
I'd like one shaved ice, please!
빙수 하나 줘!
So cold and refreshing! Shaved ice is the best!
정말 차갑고 상쾌하다! 빙수가 최고지!
You want some, Tajiri?
너도 먹을래, 다지리?
Not until you spin three times and bark.
3번 돌고 짖으면 줄게
She really did it!
얘가 정말로 했다!
-Please...? -Not yet!
- 제발... - 아직은 안 돼
Give me a paw.
손을 줘
Jashin-chan.
사신짱
Are you bullying Pekola?
페코라를 괴롭히는 거니?
It's a misunderstanding.
그건 오해야
Pekola wanted shaved ice...
페코라가 빙수를 먹고 싶어 해서...
Seems like you haven't been disciplined enough.
넌 아직도 훈육을 덜 받은 거 같아
Jashin-chan.
사신짱
You'll get sunburned like that.
저렇게 햇볕에 네 피부를 태울 거야
Here's a parasol.
자, 파라솔이야
But why are you closing it up?
그런데 파라솔은 왜 접어?
Cut!
컷!
-Yay! -Whoa! Whoa! Whoa!
- 야호! - 우와! 우와! 우와!
Here.
여기 있어
I'm sorry Jashin-chan bullied you.
사신짱이 널 괴롭혀서 미안해
Are you sure? Thanks.
정말이야? 고마워
I've been dreaming about you.
너를 꿈꿔왔어
Cold and delicious!
차갑고 맛있다!
The brain freeze feels so good!
뇌가 어는 느낌이 너무 좋다!
How's the ice?
얼음 맛이 어때요?
Devils...?
악마들...?
Shoot! This shaved ice was produced by devils.
젠장! 이건 악마가 만든 빙수였군
Does it taste good?
맛있나요?
Yes. It's very good.
네, 아주 맛있어요
I'm glad.
다행이네요
Thank you.
고마워요
What is it?
이건 뭐지?
Hey, Koji.
어이, 코지
It's rude to stare like that.
그렇게 쳐다보는 건 실례다
Look who's talking.
누가 누구더러 하는 말인지
I'll change your name to Tsugumitsu!
네 이름을 츠구미츠로 바꿀 거야
Who's that?
그게 누군데?
Noto's Suzu District military commander, Tsugumitsu Yusa!
노토의 스즈 지역 군사령관, 츠구미츠 유사!
Yusa, Koji! She's an angel!
유사, 코지! 이 애는 천사다!
Don't let your guard down, she'll kill you!
너희가 경계를 늦추면 얘가 죽일 거야
What was that?
뭐라고?
She says you're more of a threat.
코지가 그러는데 네가 더 위험하대
What?
뭐?
-You little brat, Koji Tsugumitsu! -Quit that.
- 이 쪼그만 게, 츠구미츠 코지! - 그만해
I'll skin you and rub salt all over your body.
네 가죽을 벗겨서 온몸에 소금을 문질러 줄 거다
So cold to the touch, feels good!
만지니까 아주 차갑지만 기분이 너무 좋다
Making friends with an angel? Don't make me laugh!
천사와 친구가 된다고? 웃기지 마라!
You guys are idiots!
너희들은 다 멍청이야!
Dumbasses!
바보들아!
They're all so annoying.
다들 정말 짜증 나
Such idiots.
멍청이들
Is it about time?
시간이 다 됐어?
What's that?
저건 뭐지?
It's a kraken!
크라켄이다!
-From Norse mythology? -Yup!
- 북유럽 신화에 나오는 거? - 응!
Jashin-chan!
사신짱!
Medusa!
메두사!
Hurry up and save me! Save me from...
어서 날 구해줘! 구해줘, 이게...
What's his name?
이거 이름이 뭐지?
How should I know?
내가 어떻게 알아?
Just save me!
그냥 날 구해줘
Hey, Mr. Kraken!
이봐요, 크라켄 씨!
Could you please let go of Jashin-chan?
부탁인데 사신짱을 놓아주세요
Idiot!
바보야!
Hey!
이봐!
-Jashin-chan! -Something cracked!
- 사신짱! - 뭐가 부러졌다!
If you're hungry, Medusa's a lot more flavorful than I am.
혹시 배고프시면 나보다 메두사가 훨씬 더 맛있어요
Take my spot, Medusa!
나와 자리를 바꾸자, 메두사!
I'm worth a lot more than you!
내가 너보다 훨씬 더 중요해
Look over there, big guy!
저길 봐요, 덩치 씨!
Eat that girl over there!
저기 있는 여자애를 먹어요
-Seriously? -How despicable.
- 세상에 - 진짜 비열하다
She really is.
쟤는 정말 그래
Come on, what are you waiting for?
빨리요, 뭐 하는 거죠?
Wait! Don't eat me!
잠깐, 날 먹지 말아요!
-He ate her. -Just like that.
- 저게 사신짱을 먹었다 - 갑작스럽네
Guys!
얘들아
She's still your friend, right?
저 애는 너희들 친구잖아
I know she's a sleaze, but we have to save her!
나도 쟤가 못된 건 알아 하지만 우리가 구해야 해
Change of plans.
계획 변경
-We'll have seafood tonight. -Where did that come from?
- 오늘 저녁은 해산물로 하자 - 그게 무슨 소리야?
That's fine with me.
난 좋아
Me too!
나도!
I'll cheer you on!
난 응원할게!
Let's take care of him, quick!
저놈을 처리하자, 빨리!
Devil blow!
악마의 강타다!
-Are you okay? -Yes.
- 너 괜찮니? - 응
Kraken!
크라켄!
That armor's cool! Hand it over!
멋진 갑옷이다! 그걸 넘겨!
You can't do that!
그러면 안 돼!
-How about next time? -Promise?
- 다음에 줄게 - 약속했다?
I gotta be dead, right?
난 죽은 거지?
Your body melted.
네 몸이 녹았어
Are you okay?
괜찮아?
Does it look like I am?
내가 괜찮아 보이냐?
This is all because Yurine summoned me here in the first place.
이건 애초에 유리네가 날 이리 소환해서 생긴 일이야
Or else I would've never come to the beach!
안 그랬으면 난 이 해변에 절대 안 왔어
Look at me!
날 보라고
Yurine's to blame for all of this!
이건 전부 유리네 잘못이야
I despise you...
난 널 경멸한다...
I hate you!
네가 정말 싫어
-What's happening? -Jashin-chan?
- 무슨 일이지? - 사신짱?
Give me the answer I desire!
내가 원하는 답을 주시오
Ancient woman warrior!
고대 여전사여!
Amazon!
아마존!
-Here? -Just hurry up and strip!
- 여기서? - 그냥 빨리 벗어!
This thing too!
이것도
-Take it all off! -Oh, no!
- 전부 벗어 - 안 돼
Look at me in this awesome armor!
이 멋진 갑옷을 입은 나를 봐라
You savage.
이 야만인아
Victory's mine! I'll finish her!
승리는 나의 것이다! 저 애를 없애 버릴 거야
Goodbye, Yurine!
잘 가라, 유리네!
You never learn, huh?
도무지 배우는 게 없군
Fine, I'll fight you.
좋아, 상대해 줄게
Beth!
베이트!
Beth?
베이트?
You're gonna end up dead, just like Yurine!
너도 유리네처럼 죽게 될 거다
Beth!
베이트!
I won't let you get away with this!
네가 이러고도 무사할 줄 알아?
Full Armor Jashin-chan Dropkick!
완전 무장 사신짱 드롭킥!
The battle
전투는
still
계속
continues...
진행됩니다
Looks delicious!
맛있겠다
What do you wanna eat first?
넌 뭐부터 먹을 거야?
This smells so good!
정말 맛있는 냄새야
It melts in my mouth.
입안에서 녹아
I wanna eat it all.
난 다 먹고 싶어
There we go.
됐다
Delicious!
맛있다
Who knew kraken tasted so good?
크라켄이 이렇게 맛있을 줄 누가 알았겠어?
Let me try!
나도 맛볼게
Delicious!
끝내준다!
Me too, me too!
나도, 나도
They know they're eating kraken, right?
자기들이 크라켄을 먹고 있는 걸 알겠지?
Have a bite, Pekola.
먹어 봐, 페코라
There's no way-- I mean,
절대 안 돼... 내 말은
-I'm quite full-- -Here.
- 난 배불러... - 자
Delicious!
맛있다!
Eat up, Pekola.
어서 먹어, 페코라
Here's another piece.
여기 또 있어
Yes, please.
그래, 고마워
I know you're not a lefty.
넌 왼손잡이가 아니잖아
I can feed myself, I'm not a baby!
내가 먹을 수 있어 난 아기가 아니야!
I don't need your help at all, Yurine.
네 도움은 전혀 필요 없어, 유리네
Mind your own business!
네 일이나 신경 써!
Let's have a peaceful dinner.
저녁은 평화롭게 먹자
Fine. I'll be helped.
좋아, 도움을 받지
Here, say, "Ah."
자, "아" 해봐
Really?
정말?
Shut up and eat.
조용히 하고 먹어
It's so good-- Huh?
정말 맛있다, 어?
Didn't realize you were that close with the witch.
네가 마녀와 이렇게 친한 줄 몰랐다
Tajiri!
다지리!
-They're not close. -Not at all.
- 쟤들 친한 거 아니야 - 전혀
They're intimate!
쟤들 친해!
-Not at all! -Don't be shy.
- 절대 아니야! - 부끄러워하지 마
Just admit it.
그냥 인정해라
What the hell are you talking about?
대체 무슨 소리야?
Admit it, just admit it.
인정해, 그냥 받아들이라고
Just admit it!
인정하라니까!
Damn it! You're all gonna regret this later!
젠장! 너희 모두 후회할 줄 알아!